A Rose for Christmas is a drama, tv movie, romance film directed by Kevin Fair.
Andy is a passionate artist whose family has been
building Rose Parade floats for generations.
When her Dad gets sick, Andy is forced to take the helm and supervise
the construction and decoration of their client's float.
And to make matters worse, she's saddled with the extra challenge of dealing with a
demanding businessman Cliff, whose company commissioned the float.
Andy, played by Rachel Boston.
Cliff, played by Marc Bendavid.
Lou, played by Nels Lennarson.
Mr. Ellsworth, played by Daryl Shuttleworth.
Auctioneer, played by Jenson Kerr.
Christine, played by Ali Milner.
A Christmas Prince is a 2017 Christmas romantic comedy film directed by Alex Zamm, written by Karen Schaler and Nathan Atkins,
and stars Rose McIver, Ben Lamb, Tom Knight, Sarah Douglas, Daniel Fathers, Alice Krige, and Tahirah Sharif.
The film was released on Netflix on November 17, 2017.
Two sequels, A Christmas Prince: The Royal Wedding, &, A
Christmas Prince: The Royal Baby came out a year apart.
The film explores themes of new year's eve, holiday, artist, float, christmas.
The tone is emotional.